898 Delsie Dr., Grants Pass, Or, 97527 • 541-244-8998

ray.reid@codingdojograds.com

SUMMARY:

www.linkedin.com/in/rayreid97527/

My experience is in guest relations, problem solving, and leading a team. My passion is in computer languages and building applications. I want to help a team in developing web-based services that help consumers improve their lives.

SKILLS:

HTML • CSS • JavaScript • Jquery • Bootstrap • Python • Flask • Django • MVC ASP.NetCore MySQL • AWS

ACCOMPLISHMENTS:

Teamwork

Led team to improve business profits and guest relations with team support of guest first approach. Increased sales by 20% over previous year and won beat the Boss contest for the district.

EMPLOYMENT:

Petco Grants Pass, Or.

Office Manager/Supervisor

April 2015 to June 2018

- Provided employees with guidance in handling difficult and complex problems, and in resolving escalated complaints and disputes.
- Participated in the work of subordinates in order to facilitate productivity and to overcome difficult aspects of work.

Fresh and Easy neighborhood market

San Jose, Ca.

Assistant Manager

December 2012 to March 2015

- Inventoried stock and reordered when inventory dropped to a specified level.
- Monitored sales activities to ensure that customers received satisfactory service and quality goods.

Grocery Outlet San Jose, Ca.

Retail Supervisor

September 2007 to March 2012

- Formulated pricing policies for merchandise, according to profitability requirements.
- Reviewed inventory and sales records to prepare reports for management and budget departments.

Family Ear, Nose, Throat Group

Gilroy, Ca

Lead Medical Assistant

September 2001 to February 2006

- Assisted medical practice, patients, and hospital with surgical scheduling. Worked with insurance company over benefit coverage, authorization, and billing issues.
- Administered all aspects of allergy immune therapy program for medical practice.
 Ministered injections, formulated patient therapy, tracked patient progressed, and tested allergic response.

EDUCATION:

Coding Dojo Seattle, WA. Certificate Oct 2018

<u>University of Phoenix</u> San Jose, Ca. Business Management, BS 2013